The traditional school year, with three months of vacation every summer, was first implemented when America was an agricultural society and the summer months were needed for farm work.
传统学年每年夏天放三个月假，这种安排最初实行时，美国还是农业社会，夏季那几个月需要用来干农活。
Since then, we’ve completely changed as a nation.
从那时起，我们这个国家已经彻底改变了。
Students no longer spend summers farming, but they aren’t in school, either.
学生们夏天不再务农，可也不在学校上学。
The average American student receives 13 weeks off from school each calendar year—with about 11 of those during the summer.
美国学生平均每个日历年有13周不用上学，其中约11周在夏季。
Few other countries have more than seven weeks off in a school calendar.
很少有其他国家的校历假期超过七周。
With the US lagging behind other countries in academics, it’s time to consider year-round schooling.
美国在学业上落后于其他国家，是时候考虑全年制上学了。
One benefit of this change is that students will not fall victim to the “summer slide,” or the well-documented phenomenon where students forget some of the knowledge they have acquired when too much time is taken off from school.
这一改变的一个好处是，学生不会再陷入“暑期滑坡”，也就是一种已被大量研究证实的现象：离开学校的时间太长，学生就会忘掉一部分已经学到的知识。
Decades of research shows that it can take from 8 to 13 weeks at the beginning of every school year for students to get back to where they were before the summer holiday.
数十年的研究表明，每学年开始时，学生可能需要8到13周才能恢复到暑假前的水平。
But year-round schooling isn’t just about academics.
但全年制上学不只关乎学业。
Teachers and students experience a closer relationship in year-round schools than they do in traditional schools and, in the absence of any long-term break, students do not feel detached from the school environment.
在全年制学校里，师生关系比在传统学校里更亲密；而且由于没有任何长假，学生不会感到与学校环境疏离。
These closer bonds and greater attachment pay off.
这些更紧密的纽带和更深的依恋都会带来回报。
Research shows that students in year-round schools are more self-confident and feel more positive about their schooling experience.
研究表明，全年制学校的学生更自信，对自己的上学经历也抱有更积极的看法。
But don’t kids need time to relax?
可是，孩子们难道不需要时间放松吗？
Some childhood development experts believe that time off from school is vital to healthy development as kids are not designed to spend so much of their time inside classrooms and the summer break provides a perfect opportunity to get outside.
一些儿童发展专家认为，放假不上学对健康成长至关重要，因为孩子天生就不适合把这么多时间花在教室里，而暑假提供了到户外去的绝佳机会。
The problem with this argument is that most children aren’t playing outside or even spending time with other kids.
这种观点的问题在于，大多数孩子并没有在户外玩耍，甚至没有和其他孩子待在一起。
While some children visit summer camps, most stay at home, watching TV or playing games on electronic devices, which hardly benefits them.
虽然有些孩子会去参加夏令营，但大多数都待在家里，看电视或在电子设备上玩游戏，这对他们几乎没有好处。
The US has changed from a farming economy to a knowledge- and innovation-based economy, so it makes sense for the school year to change as well.
美国已经从农业经济转变为以知识和创新为基础的经济，因此学年也随之改变是合乎情理的。